YOU AND EVERYTHING ELSE
I'm telling you, she hit my palms.
- Really?
- Yes!
Yes. I hit her really hard.
And you didn't even know it was me.
But you got your revenge, didn't you?
As for her, she always targeted me
during dodgeball.
Fess up.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
- Yeah. I think I did.
- Seriously?
I still can't believe it.
What are the chances we'd meet here?
I know, right?
You should have told me earlier
that you had such a beautiful friend.
Your phone's ringing.
Stop avoiding your girlfriend's calls.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, go.
Sorry, my phone was on silent. What's up?
- Come here!
- Yeah.
- See how I look out for you?
- Sure. It's nice to meet you.
We met at the booth. I'm Kim Sang-hak.
Business management. Class of 2000.
I know.
I'm Cheon Sang-yeon.
Engineering. Class of 2002.
Whenever he would say his name,
I felt conscious of Sang-yeon.
But Sang-yeon didn't seem to care at all
about something as trivial as a name.
Why didn't you stay in touch
if you were so close?
Can't you find old friends
on I Love You School?
You're right.
I actually looked you up ages ago.
Didn't you look me up?
I didn't go on those sites.
Really? Almost everyone has
a profile on I Love You School.
I never really loved school, you see.
Also, I wasn't even in school back then.
So you missed high school entirely?
I attended for two months or so,
then quit.
Wait, do you really have a Leica?
It's my older brother's.
Is he a photographer?
As a hobby, I guess.
How old is he? How can he afford a Leica?
- I know.
- He's 4 years older than me, so he's 25.
He just left the military,
so he's still in university.
What's his major?
Guys, stop asking questions.
What is this, a hearing?
- Business management.
- No way. Me too!
Sang-hak here too.
What university is he at?
Seoul University.
Sang-yeon spoke of her brother
with such ease.
As though Sang-hak were really alive
and well somewhere.
Eun-jung, have you met her older brother?
Is he handsome?
What? Yeah, I've seen him.
He's handsome. Really handsome.
Who's more handsome?
Sang-hak oppa here or Sang-yeon's oppa?
Kim Sang-hak seonbae is far more handsome.
Jeez, come on.
I told you to stop bringing up my looks.
People will think
that's all I have to offer.
Come on, put him in his place.
Your boyfriend's getting cocky again.
Okay. Well, your facial features
are well-proportioned,
but you're not that good-looking.
Okay, duly noted. I get it.
God, you're so funny.
These two are dating, by the way.
Wow, really? You guys look good together.
- Do we?
- Yeah.
That hurt my pride.
Honestly, you're not that handsome.
Brilliant. So funny.
Where do you have to be this late?
I have a part-time job.
No one could cover her shift.
How will you get there?
- Subway.
- I'm taking the subway too.
- Goodbye, then.
- Bye, guys.
Dae-kyu, didn't you say
you'd stay for round three?
- Bye, guys.
- Bye!
Let's go for another round!
- Are you that happy?
- Yeah.
But it all feels like a blur.
Maybe because I still can't believe it.
I think we'll have a lot to talk about
when I see her tomorrow.
Do you remember that photo
from one of your old exhibitions?
I thought it was Sang-yeon in that photo.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hold up.
Jeez, Ryu Eun-jung.
Why didn't you ever mention her to me
if you were so close with her?
Didn't I? I can't really remember.
You can't really remember?
You always spoke of Na-mi and Ju-eun,
but I never heard about Cheon Sang-yeon.
Oh, I don't know.
It's all so complicated.
I'll tell you next time.
Will you actually?
Of course I will.
Because I can't talk about my life
without mentioning Cheon Sang-yeon.
And going forward, you won't be able to
discuss your life without mentioning me.
That's true even now.
Even now, I can't talk about my life
without mentioning you, silly.
"Silly"?
Yes, "silly."
I bet you didn't know
that's what I call you in my diary.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Come here. Bring it on, you.
Sang-yeon!
Hey.
She resigned from school?
Yeah. Complaints from parents
were pouring in.
Complaints?
I guess she was a homeroom teacher
who didn't care about her students.
Ms. Yoon didn't care about her students?
She's not the Ms. Yoon you remember.
Really?
You know we went bankrupt, right?
What?
Yeah.
What about you? Where do you live?
I still live in the same neighborhood.
We moved to a different house though.
It's two streets over from my old house.
My mom runs a rice cake shop.
Remember Daeseong's Mill
in your old apartment complex?
Yeah.
She runs it with my uncle.
Right, I see.
My mom and dad got divorced.
After the divorce,
Mom and I moved to Gangneung.
And your dad still lives in Seoul?
I don't know. We don't stay in touch.
I see.
I thought we'd have so much to say,
but I was flustered by how awkward it was.
Perhaps those five years
had taken something away from us.
See you around.
Yeah. Good luck with that paper.
Sang-yeon?
Can I ask…
why you didn't tell me
you were moving back then?
Were you upset with me or something?
No. Why?
Ju-eun called me to say
it looked like your family was moving,
so I rushed over to your place,
but you had already left.
I paged you, but you never replied.
You even changed your pager number.
I told you that we went bankrupt.
How could I contact you
when we were practically running away?
Still, I thought that if I waited,
I'd hear from you. But I never did.
Dad told me not to contact anyone
and got rid of my pager.
I see.
So you weren't mad at me or something?
Of course not.
I'm happy to see you again.
I mean it.
I am too.
My mom's even more excited than I am.
She keeps asking when you’ll come visit.
Really?
I'd love to see her too.
Tell her I’ll come visit
as soon as I get a day off work.
Sure. Mom would love that.
I'll see you later.
See you.
Where is your friend Cheon Sang-yeon?
She's working.
Gosh, she sure has a lot on her plate.
Does she even have time
for club activities?
Who knows?
Hurry. The food's delicious.
I'll take that. Thank you.
Do you cook at home?
Yeah. I cook at least one meal a day.
It's usually just putting rice
in the cooker. I keep it simple.
It's good you eat
at least one meal at home.
I tried to stop Mom
in case you might not eat at home.
She insisted her anchovies aren't salty
and you could eat them without rice.
I do love your mom's cooking.
But tell her not to cook for me next time.
My fridge is tiny,
so I don't have much space.
I already told her not to.
Let's stop to use the toilet.
Okay, go ahead.
You should come too.
I don't need to go.
Come with me anyway.
I really don't need to go.
I don't have a toilet at home, that's why.
You don't have a toilet?
There is one, but it's a squat toilet.
- Careful.
- Okay.
That's the toilet.
I can take back anything you don't want.
I'm going to eat it all.
I'm almost done.
Take your time.
I couldn't quite believe
that this was Sang-yeon's room.
Hey, this is really good.
Try some.
- Good, right?
- They're okay.
Oh, those. The hinge broke.
I can see that.
It's all right.
It's payday today, so I'll buy a new pair
first thing tomorrow.
Other than the toilet issue,
this place is decent.
The rent's affordable too. 80,000 won.
That is affordable.
This is so good.
Are you sure it's okay to drink
before your shift?
It's just a beer.
I don't have to be there until 9:00,
so it's fine.
Work won't be a problem,
but going to the toilet will be.
I'm fine using that toilet.
We had a squat toilet until fourth grade.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I always thought that squat toilets
only existed in places like folk villages.
I am a little shocked that there's still
a squat toilet here in Seoul in 2002.
That's why I don't eat after 7 p.m.
To avoid using the toilet.
The toilets we went to earlier
close at 10:00 p.m.
You know what was
a real culture shock for me?
Seeing two bathrooms in your old house.
Maybe I have zero bathrooms now
because I had two back then.
The thing is,
I didn't even know my family was poor
until fourth grade.
It only hit me after the city developments
and our move to a semi-basement.
I really liked your old house.
Don't be ridiculous.
You said I was the first.
I was the only one you invited.
That's why you liked it?
Yeah.
How silly.
Anyway,
I think being poor is all relative.
I think it's absolute.
If you have no money,
there's nothing you can do.
Absolutely nothing.
The world is a place
that offers even less
to those who are most desperate.
Think about it. I had two bathrooms
when I didn't even need them,
but now I have none.
And now I'm at a good university,
but I can't find students to tutor.
You'll find students.
I do hope so.
How could you drink so much
with someone who has to go to work?
She only had one beer.
I ended up having three beers, maybe?
That's a lie. I had four.
Seems like you had fun though.
Yeah, it was fun.
But the alcohol was…
Maybe because it all felt a little bleak…
Bleak? Why?
Sang-yeon, she…
Never mind.
I think I'll cry if I talk about it.
What's new? You always cry.
Exactly. I absolutely hate crying
while talking,
but I just can't stop myself.
So I'd rather not say.
You'll blab eventually.
I so won't.
It all looked a little lonely.
Sang-yeon
and her place.
I'm not going to cry.
You think I'm a big crybaby, don't you?
Yikes, you're sensitive.
Look. No tears, right?
Why, I'm so proud of you.
Sang-yeon says she likes your photo.
- My photo?
- Yes.
She's seen my photos?
She must have gone to the clubroom
during some free time.
She asked who took the photo of the chair
that was on the wall.
She must have an eye for photography.
I agree.
Don't you have some prints of that?
Yeah, I do.
Let's give her one.
Okay, sure.
And she's coming to the seminar.
- The seminar?
- I bragged about you presenting.
If she comes to anything,
she should come on a photography trip.
No. You're most admirable
when you're leading your seminars.
Do you want her to admire me?
Of course.
Boy, I do hope she doesn't
complicate things by falling for me.
Don't worry. She won't.
She won't?
Yes. She would never.
Excuse me? I feel strangely offended.
Why wouldn't she?
She has high standards.
Hey!
I'm just saying she'll be there.
So make sure to do your best.
Okay, I'll do my best.
I understand that we cannot verify
the photo's authenticity
because the photographer,
as well as the witnesses,
gave inconsistent testimonies.
But what does that have to do
with the photographer's integrity?
It has everything to do with it.
If a photo's authenticity is questionable,
of course, it's a matter of integrity.
Why is this even a question?
Okay. Let's say a moment of greed
led to a manipulated photo,
or they accepted
the editor's manipulation of the photo.
Regardless, the photographer is
responsible for any deceptive photos.
No excuses. How can you deny that?
I don't mean to deny that.
The point I'm trying to make here is…
To be honest, the reason I find
your presentation mind-numbingly dull
is that from the start, you've portrayed
the photographer in a negative light.
It's irrational.
Dude, this is crazy.
I'm irrational?
Do you really think that artists
can be separated from their art?
He'd already been outsmarted,
but I still hoped
he'd turn it around using reason.
We're talking about war photography here.
It's documentary work.
People have already accepted
these photos as truth.
Now, that's completely off the mark.
How am I off the mark?
This was the point from the beginning.
How is that even relevant?
Defeated.
Did she come here to pick a fight?
She never shows up for club activities,
then comes to pick a fight?
She wasn't picking a fight.
Gosh, my head hurts.
How embarrassing.
Who do you think was right?
You can do better next time.
Don't think about it too much.
So you agree with her, then?
She totally crushed me.
You had fun?
Yeah. How should I put it?
It felt like I was finally
a true university student.
Your boyfriend's presentation
was so interesting.
Seriously?
- Didn't you find it interesting?
- It was interesting, all right.
Did I act like a snob again?
Yeah.
Goodness! When did you become so pretty?
- Have you been well, Mrs. Jang?
- Of course.
You look so beautiful.
So will you take the tutoring job?
Yes. Thank you for the recommendation.
Oh, don't mention it.
I didn't do anything.
The piano academy owner upstairs
needed a tutor for her kids,
so I mentioned you.
Are they in high school?
Yes, her daughter is.
Her son's in middle school,
and he'll be bringing a friend.
Wow, I didn't know it would be three kids!
- Seonbae.
- Hello.
Welcome, Sang-hak.
Hello.
Yeah, hi. Long time no see.
I'm so excited that the three of us
are drinking together.
Hold up. Are you feeling shy?
As if.
You so are!
No way. Is this because of the seminar?
Hey.
Don't talk about the seminar.
The topic is off-limits.
Sang-yeon said
she found your presentation interesting.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
It was interesting, actually.
Interesting or not, the point is
that the photo was manipulated.
I never said that it wasn't.
If you agree, then why did you--
That's enough.
I have to agree with Sang-yeon
about the seminar.
Let's change the subject.
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers.
By the way,
didn't you bring that photo that day?
You did, didn't you?
You brought it, right?
No comment.
What?
The chair photo that you said you liked.
My boyfriend brought that photo for you,
but you put him through that ordeal.
"The reason I find your presentation
mind-numbingly dull is…"
Oh dear. God, I'm so sorry.
Could I have that photo, please?
It depends.
I'll do my best. Please?
I'll be watching you closely.
Okay.
- Cheers.
Once Sang-yeon started tutoring,
we began to hang out almost every day.
- One, two, three.
- Let's do this!
Let's go!
Hurry up! Come on!
Pass it to me!
Nice shot!
Hey, it's fine.
I'll switch. Switch with me. You're in.
Good luck!
- Go.
- Hello, oppa.
Hey.
Hey. Why do you call everyone else "oppa"
but your boyfriend "seonbae"?
Since orientation, I've called
the upperclassmen in my major "oppa,"
whereas I've called Sang-hak "seonbae"
since I first signed up for the club.
Yeah, but why?
You're the only girl in our year
who calls him "seonbae."
Everyone calls him "oppa."
That's because…
I could never bring myself
to call him "Sang-hak oppa."
Doesn't it sound kind of cool?
"Seonbae. Sang-hak seonbae."
But still, calling your boyfriend
"seonbae" is a bit…
She calls him "seonbae" too, you know.
Is it some weird custom
from your hometown?
I bet her reasons for calling him that
are similar to mine.
By the way, how come she never dates?
She isn't seeing anyone, is she?
I'm not sure.
Do you know why Byeong-gi and Dae-kyu
are nowhere to be seen these days?
They asked her out,
but she flat-out refused.
Byeong-gi liked Sang-yeon too?
I doubt he's the only one.
I'm pretty sure everyone from her cohort
is interested in her.
I'm not surprised.
She's always been popular.
I wonder if she really
isn't interested in anyone.
Do you think
there's anyone in our photography club
that Sang-yeon might like?
Kim Sang-hak?
What?
What do you mean, "What?"
You asked whether there was anyone
she might like, and I think there is.
This isn't about
whether they'll go out or not.
There's just
a vibe, you know?
Then do you think Sang-hak seonbae…
Forget it.
I knew you'd react like this.
Be honest. You're curious, aren't you?
About whether he's even
the slightest bit interested in her.
Not at all! You're so mean.
I'm right, aren't I?
Did you miss it?
They actually scored a goal.
Stop lying, man. Who would have known
that Lee Chun-soo would deliver?
Right?
Why? Did Lee Chun-soo score?
Yeah. He got past the defense
and the goalie in the penalty area.
Really?
What if we get to the final 16?
Fat chance. In terms of physicality,
the opponents are on a different level.
…he gets in the car after their fight.
Yeah, and he comes back later.
But Arnie disappears, causing chaos.
- Right.
- I swear DiCaprio is…
Sang-hak and Sang-yeon
clicked in many ways.
Especially regarding movies.
Why would you talk about movies
in a photography club?
They should have joined
a movie club instead.
Ta-da. I bought us all ice cream.
- Nice.
- How much?
- 10,000 won bet.
- 10,000? Okay, you're on.
- Did you buy vanilla?
- Of course!
Hey, save the chocolate-coated one
for Eun-jung.
I want vanilla!
Guys, what should you say?
- Thank you.
- That's more like it.
- Vanilla, yum.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- You're on.
Eat this. Just take what you're given.
Why don't you date?
- What?
- Does nobody strike your fancy?
I do have a crush.
You do?
Yeah.
Who is it?
Well,
someone I met in an online chat room
while I was in Gangneung.
"Online chat room"?
If you were in Gangneung, that was
ages ago. Why aren't you dating him?
You can't date all of your crushes.
If it's you, then yeah.
Who would pass you up?
It wasn't mutual.
Man, I'm annoyed.
It was an unrequited crush.
"Unrequited crush"?
Do you know what he looks like?
Yes.
I followed him around.
Followed him around?
Secretly.
I stalked him.
Why? You should have
confessed your feelings.
He has a girlfriend.
Oh… That's too bad.
What kind of person is he?
Is he handsome?
He got me to fall for him,
so I guess he wasn't ugly.
I'm really curious about
what kind of person you would be drawn to.
It's all in the past now.
I'm going to find someone new.
Okay. Keep your eyes peeled.
For what?
It's nothing.
STORIES ON MOVIES
- You're reading about movies?
- Holy crap!
God, you scared me.
Why were you so surprised?
- When did you get here?
- Last night.
- What?
- I developed almost a hundred photos.
Want to see?
It's such a delicate process,
so I kept getting different results.
It was driving me nuts.
Then it suddenly clicked.
Look there.
Those ones made the cut.
Which one is the best?
Oh, well, they all look similar to me.
They do?
I can't seem to pick one.
You developed this one photo all night?
Yeah. Developing photos is so much fun.
I could never beat her.
These photos turned out really well.
Each one is great in its own unique way.
Maybe it's the camera.
Cameras don't take photos by themselves.
I couldn't pick the best one out of these.
Whoa, you did a great job
developing these.
All three are unique,
but each one has a vibrant color gradient.
Which one do you guys like?
- Let's show this in our August exhibit.
- This one?
All the emotions I'd forgotten
came flooding back.
You could go pro, Sang-yeon.
Ms. Pro.
Being around Sang-yeon
makes everything about me
feel so ordinary.
Insignificant, even.
I'd like to express emotions…
Why didn't you share your photos?
Didn't you develop the photos
of the rice cake and side dish shops?
I did. I developed them, but…
Let's see them.
You said you'd pick one for the exhibit.
I might just go with something else.
Something else?
Yeah.
They’re all just photos of people,
so they feel a bit too simple.
How so? I think they'd be great.
What is it?
What's got you feeling down?
It's just
your photos have a special something,
and so do Sang-yeon's.
Mine seem too ordinary in comparison.
They do?
Yeah.
When I look at the two of you,
it’s clear how talented
and curious you both are.
I bet you'll both succeed
in whatever you do.
And you won't?
No.
What is it you want to do?
Me?
I'm not really good at anything--
You're eloquent.
How am I eloquent?
Come on. Don't be like that
over something so small.
You have me, don't you?
What?
What's that supposed to mean?
- What is it?
- What did you mean by that?
Mean by what?
- I just--
- Do you think you're all I need?
Eun-jung.
No matter how much I like you
or how proud I am
to call you my boyfriend,
your achievements are yours, not mine.
That's not what I meant. I just think
your photos are perfectly fine--
Perfectly fine isn't good enough!
Eun-jung.
There are things even he can't do.
He could never calm this anxiety.
I wanted to know.
I wanted to line up
all the 21-year-olds in the world
to know where I stood amongst them.
To know what I was capable of
and what I couldn't dream of doing.
Why aren't you answering? Please pick up.
I need you to talk to me.
But I really do admire the things you say.
Your photos too.
They're not just fine.
They're really good.
I just woke up,
and I'm feeling pretty embarrassed.
I'm sorry I took my anger out on you.
You managed to rest, did you?
I'm sorry.
I'll forgive you
because you seem really sorry.
Okay.
Let's see.
You're wearing this?
I forgot! Give me one minute.
- Just one minute!
- Okay.
Go, Korea!
In June of that year,
the entire country was buzzing.
Go, Korea!
Ahn Jung-hwan shoots! And he scores!
Ahn Jung-hwan!
Hong Myung-bo!
He shoots, and he scores!
Korea is through to the semifinals!
Team Korea is through to the semis!
The actual semifinals!
This is incredible.
A very emotional moment for us all.
What were you thinking about earlier?
Earlier when?
During the shoot-out.
I'm not too sure.
What was I thinking about again?
I guess I was thinking,
"People really like this kind of stuff."
That sort of thing.
Don't you like this?
Of course I do. It's the semifinals.
Eun-jung, do you ever feel that way?
As if you snap and break away.
Feeling detached, I suppose.
You strive to pretend,
trying to make something your reality,
but you simply can't keep up
and just come to a halt.
Like being snapped away.
Are you reminded of your brother?
Cheon Sang-hak?
Yeah.
I've been meaning to ask you.
You always talk as if--
He's still alive?
Yeah.
There must be people
who knew him in the past
who are still unaware that he's gone.
They must think that he's somewhere,
alive and well.
Or since they assume he's well,
maybe he never even crosses their minds?
It's like that for me too.
He never even crosses my mind.
Eun-jung, let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
I can't help but like you.
So annoying.
Why? What is?
Forget it.
What do you mean, what?
You're annoying, of course.
- What did I do to annoy--
- I'm annoyed.
Cheon Sang-yeon, you're so annoying.
Hey, what did I do?
BALANCE: 723,254 WON
Only 720,000 won?
Hello, sir.
Welcome.
- I'd like to sell these books.
- Sure.
Mom, please.
No.
Come on, Mom. Please?
I said no.
It's just that--
Hey! No means no!
Why would you move out
when you have a perfectly good home?
- If you think about--
- Zip it!
Lift your foot. And the other one.
- Sir, I only rode this a few times.
- I see.
So these brakes are practically new.
Well, even so…
40,000 won should be reasonable.
But this bike changes gears, and--
The tires are pretty much flat.
- But filling them with air costs nothing.
- That's not true.
Come on, please? Mom, please.
Move it.
Why don't you just sell everything off?
Why not sell me off too?
I just need you to pitch in
one million won.
On second thought, just 500,000. Please?
Come on. It's Sang-yeon.
How much is the deposit?
- 500,000 won.
- 500,000?
Then let's add 2.5 million to that
and find a place with a 3 million deposit.
Is your mom really okay with this?
Of course, she said no at first.
But she changed her mind
when I said I'd be living with you.
- I would love that, but--
- That's settled, then.
Let's start searching tomorrow.
There's that photography trip next week…
Are you really not coming this time?
It's a trip to Gangneung.
Why would I go there?
But still…
It's Sang-hak's last trip
before joining the military.
He's going to the military?
Yes.
When?
July 16th, so in just three weeks.
I'm not going in.
Sang-yeon, there's something
really cool over there.
- Whoa, no way!
- No way!
In you go!
Guys! How could you?
It's so cold.
Why is it so cold in the summer?
Because it's technically not summer.
It's still June.
Aren't you glad you came?
No. What was I thinking
when I agreed to come here?
I know you're having fun.
Now that I'm here,
I would love to see Ms. Yoon.
Should we pay her a quick visit
before dinner?
No.
We're here anyway. Wouldn't she be upset?
She doesn't even know we're here.
Why would she be upset?
Was it supposed to be a secret?
I actually called her earlier.
A secret to whom?
Ms. Yoon. Sang-yeon's mom.
Did you tell her that we're here?
She didn’t answer, so I couldn't tell her.
I just didn’t realize it was a secret.
It's Ms. Yoon.
Hello, Ms. Yoon.
I just thought I'd give you a call.
I hear your mother's a great person.
My mom?
Eun-jung says your mom is the person
she respects the most.
She said she always felt timid at school
because she didn't have a father,
but your mom helped fill that void.
She filled that void?
Yes, Ms. Yoon. I'll come visit you soon.
Of course. Take care.
I didn't tell her we're here.
Let's go see my mom, then.
You should come too.
I don't get you. I even lied
because you asked me not to tell her.
We'll say it's a surprise.
Are you sure it's okay
to just show up like this?
Maybe I should wait outside.
My mom will be happy to see you.
Who is it?
It's me.
Sang-yeon, is that you?
Yeah.
Why, you should have called
to say you were coming.
Eun-jung.
Ms. Yoon.
It's so good to see you.
What brought you all this way?
Hello, ma'am. I am…
This is Sang-hak oppa.
We're in the same photography club.
Did I mention that my brother is
also named Sang-hak? Cheon Sang-hak.
Where are my manners?
Please come inside. Come in.
Come this way.
- Please take a seat here.
- Yes.
Right here.
If I'd known you were coming,
I would have bought some food.
It's fine. We had a late lunch,
so you don't need to put anything out.
All I have is plum extract.
I love plum extract.
Are you close with your mom?
- Well…
- My mom is super close with my brother.
I bet she loves him
more than anyone else in the entire world.
- We need one more…
- Right.
I'm sorry I had no food.
It’s fine. We’re having a barbecue,
so we'll be eating soon anyway.
All right, then. Take care.
Eun-jung, you too.
I'll call.
Okay.
Eun-jung?
TO SANG-HAK OPPA
Do you remember this?
I couldn't throw away
such a beautiful letter.
I don't think Sang-hak even knew
that it was there.
I know it wasn't mine to read.
I'm sorry I read it
without your permission.
You said your father
gave you that clover, right?
Yes.
Thank you for gifting
something so precious to my son.
I'm sorry.
Eun-jung.
They are taking a long time.
They do this every time they meet.
They're practically best friends.
That was an exaggeration.
Her favorite student?
Eun-jung was my mom's favorite
even though she wasn't in her class.
I suppose it was all worth it
since Eun-jung still considers Mom
an amazing person.
It makes sense since Mom even
played favorites with her children.
She clearly preferred my brother to me.
She never tried to hide it.
Some kind of mom, isn't she?
You can stop talking.
It must have been tough.
Of course it was tough.
I deserve to be more rebellious.
My mom would have no right to judge me.
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi